<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>amzshop.net</title>
    <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/</link>
    <description>amzshop.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>orangemonkey001@outlook (Ella)</managingEditor>
      <webMaster>orangemonkey001@outlook (Ella)</webMaster><copyright>amzshop.net</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
  <title>[Brand] Solid Teak Wood Patio Bistro Set, Folding Power Coating Frame Outdoor Patio Furniture Sets, 3 Piece Patio Set of Foldable Patio Table and Chairs with 2 cushions</title>
  <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w685-w68533351/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Ella</author>
  <guid>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w685-w68533351/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[PRODUCT TITLE[Brand] Solid Teak Wood Patio Bistro Set, Folding Power Coating Frame Outdoor Patio Furniture Sets, 3 Piece Patio Set of Foldable Patio Table and Chairs with 2 cushions DescriptionSolid Teak Wood Patio Bistro Set
Bistro Set includes two folding chairs size 15.7&quot; L x 15.4&quot; W x 31.1&quot; H and one folding table size 21.7&quot; L x 21.3&rsquo; W x 28&quot; H. The main material is solid teak wood and black metal frame with powder coating.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>[VIDEO] 5 Tier Bookcase Home Office Open Bookshelf, Vintage Industrial Style Shelf with Metal Frame, MDF Board</title>
  <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/n725-wf286176aab/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Ella</author>
  <guid>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/n725-wf286176aab/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[PRODUCT TITLE[VIDEO] 5 Tier Bookcase Home Office Open Bookshelf, Vintage Industrial Style Shelf with Metal Frame, MDF Board DescriptionMore Information
Color
Black
Style
Industrial
Material
MDF Board &amp; Steel Frame
Capacity
80lbs Per Shelf
Number of Shelf Tiers
5
Foot Pad
Adjustable (1-1.5cm)
Anti-falling Device
Yes
Package Included
Bookcase &amp; Screw Pack &amp; Instruction[Five-tier Shelf Storage] The open design of this bookcase combines the charm of both minimalist and vintage furniture styles.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>[VIDEO] 5 Tier Bookcase Home Office Open Bookshelf, Vintage Industrial Style Shelf with Metal Frame, MDF Board</title>
  <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/n725-wf286176aak/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Ella</author>
  <guid>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/n725-wf286176aak/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[PRODUCT TITLE[VIDEO] 5 Tier Bookcase Home Office Open Bookshelf, Vintage Industrial Style Shelf with Metal Frame, MDF Board DescriptionMore Information
Color
White
Style
Industrial
Material
MDF Board &amp; Steel Frame
Capacity
80lbs Per Shelf
Number of Shelf Tiers
5
Foot Pad
Adjustable (1-1.5cm)
Anti-falling Device
Yes
Package Included
Bookcase &amp; Screw Pack &amp; Instruction[Five-tier Shelf Storage] The open design of this bookcase combines the charm of both minimalist and vintage furniture styles.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>[VIDEO] 5 Tier Bookcase Home Office Open Bookshelf, Vintage Industrial Style Shelf with Metal Frame, MDF Board</title>
  <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/n725-wf286176aat/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Ella</author>
  <guid>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/n725-wf286176aat/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[PRODUCT TITLE[VIDEO] 5 Tier Bookcase Home Office Open Bookshelf, Vintage Industrial Style Shelf with Metal Frame, MDF Board DescriptionMore Information
Color
Brown
Style
Industrial
Material
MDF Board &amp; Steel Frame
Capacity
80lbs Per Shelf
Number of Shelf Tiers
5
Foot Pad
Adjustable (1-1.5cm)
Anti-falling Device
Yes
Package Included
Bookcase &amp; Screw Pack &amp; Instruction[Five-tier Shelf Storage] The open design of this bookcase combines the charm of both minimalist and vintage furniture styles.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>1.1/1.6 GPF Dual Flush 1-Piece Elongated Toilet with Soft-Close Seat - Gloss White,  Water-Saving, Modern, Stylish Design 23T01-GW</title>
  <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w1573-w1573101058/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Ella</author>
  <guid>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w1573-w1573101058/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[PRODUCT TITLE1.1/1.6 GPF Dual Flush 1-Piece Elongated Toilet with Soft-Close Seat - Gloss White, Water-Saving, Modern, Stylish Design 23T01-GW DescriptionDual-Flush Functionality: Choose between two flushing options - a partial flush for liquid waste and a full flush for solid waste. This intelligent water-saving feature promotes sustainability while reducing water consumption and utility costs. Elongated Comfort: The elongated shape of the toilet bowl enhances comfort and provides ample seating space. Enjoy a more ergonomic and relaxing experience compared to traditional round-shaped toilets.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>10x10 Ft Outdoor Patio Garden Gazebo Canopy, Outdoor Shading, Gazebo Tent With Curtains</title>
  <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w419-w41941150/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Ella</author>
  <guid>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w419-w41941150/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[ PRODUCT TITLE10x10 Ft Outdoor Patio Garden Gazebo Canopy, Outdoor Shading, Gazebo Tent With Curtains Description ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>10x10 Ft Outdoor Patio Garden Gazebo Canopy, Outdoor Shading, Gazebo Tent With Curtains</title>
  <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w419-w41941372/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Ella</author>
  <guid>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w419-w41941372/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[PRODUCT TITLE10x10 Ft Outdoor Patio Garden Gazebo Canopy, Outdoor Shading, Gazebo Tent With Curtains DescriptionDescription
This outdoor patio gazebo expands your living space by moving the indoors outside to create an end-of-the-day oasis that&rsquo;s the perfect spot for entertaining family and friends. This patio gazebo designed with an elegant curved will creates the perfect and attractive outdoor setting. Enjoy the extra shading of this patio gazebo. Keep your outdoor events have a secure shelter with strong foot pads for optimal support, sturdy steel frame draping with zipper cascading curtains that can be closed to completely cover all four sides.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>10x10 Outdoor Patio Gazebo Canopy Tent With Ventilated Double Roof And Mosquito net(Detachable Mesh Screen On All Sides),Suitable for Lawn, Garden, Backyard and Deck,Brown Top</title>
  <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w419-w41940786/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Ella</author>
  <guid>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w419-w41940786/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[PRODUCT TITLE10x10 Outdoor Patio Gazebo Canopy Tent With Ventilated Double Roof And Mosquito net(Detachable Mesh Screen On All Sides),Suitable for Lawn, Garden, Backyard and Deck,Brown Top DescriptionDescription
This 10 x 10Ft gazebo provides spacious space and is fitted with four-sided mesh for insect protection and wind and rain protection.With it you will enjoy a comfortable and relaxing courtyard life with your family and friends. The double roof increases air circulation and stability, and the triangular structure of the screen supports the frame design, which is not only good-looking but also practical.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>10x20 Heavy Duty Carport Gazebo, Canopy Garage, Car Shelter with windows</title>
  <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w465-w465s00001/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Ella</author>
  <guid>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w465-w465s00001/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[PRODUCT TITLE10x20 Heavy Duty Carport Gazebo, Canopy Garage, Car Shelter with windows DescriptionQuick and easy setup
2 removable sidewalls &amp; 2 removable doors for cross ventilation and venting.
heavy duty 38mm powder coated tube
size 10x20x9ft
160g PE UV protected ,waterproof
multifunction use,wedding, birthday party, graduation party, flea markets, car tent, family parties, picnics, sports events, outdoor vendors, craft fairs, job sites and camping trips, etc.
Packaging
1xsteel frame]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>13 Bathroom Vanity with Sink, Freestanding Bathroom Vanity with Soft Close Door and Shelf(Top:BAB101MOWH)</title>
  <link>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w999-w999s00031/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 17:36:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Ella</author>
  <guid>https://blog.usa.amzshop.net/high_rated/w999-w999s00031/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[PRODUCT TITLE13 Bathroom Vanity with Sink, Freestanding Bathroom Vanity with Soft Close Door and Shelf(Top:BAB101MOWH) DescriptionSmall Floor Mounted Vanity
The freestanding design, bold and minimalist, adds a sleek look to any bathroom. Soft closing door, and the internal design is non-adjustable laminate, which can provide classified storage for daily necessities.
Ceramic Art Sink &amp; White Flat Stone Slab
The ceramic vessel sink offers long-lasting use. The combination of sink and slate, the smooth surface is easy to clean and remove stains.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
